Guide to the Peter E. Palmquist Collection of Photography and Photographic Formats
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Photographic Prints by Male Photographers, circa 1860-circa 1930; Series V; 6.9; (27 boxes)
  - Photographic Prints by Photographers East of the Mississippi River
    - New York
      - Price, F. L.; Dundee (Box 121, Folder 1339)
      - Rabineau; Albany (Box 121, Folder 1340)
      - Robinson; Trumansburgh (Box 121, Folder 1341)
      - Robinson, A.; New York City (Box 121, Folder 1342)
      - Sarony, Napoleon; New York City (Box 121, Folder 1343)
      - Schoonmaker; Troy (Box 121, Folder 1344)
      - Scidmore, D.; Gloversville (Box 121, Folder 1345)
      - Slee Brothers; Poughkeepsie (Box 121, Folder 1346)
      - Somes, A.; Schenectady (Box 121, Folder 1347)
      - Squiers, G. W.; Rochester (Box 121, Folder 1348)
      - Statham Brothers; Weedsport (Box 121, Folder 1349)
      - Tallman, C. W.; Batavia (Box 121, Folder 1350)
      - Taylor, Thomas W.; Brooklyn (Box 121, Folder 1351)
      - Thompson; Albany (Box 121, Folder 1352)
      - Thurne; G. W.; New York City (Box 121, Folder 1353)
      - Tomlinson; Elmira (Box 121, Folder 1354)
      - Turner, A. A.; New York City (Box 121, Folder 1355)
      - Tuttle; Sodus (Box 121, Folder 1356)
      - Upham, J. W.; Jamestown (Box 121, Folder 1357)
      - Vail, J. G.; Geneva (Box 121, Folder 1358)
      - Vail, J. P.; Palmyra (Box 121, Folder 1359)
      - Velten, H.; New York City (Box 121, Folder 1360)
      - Wells, M. B.; Silver Creek (Box 121, Folder 1361)
      - Wurst, O. C.; New York City (Box 121, Folder 1362)
      - Young; Hornellsville (Box 121, Folder 1363)
      - Young and Brownell; Schenevus (Box 121, Folder 1364)
    - North Carolina
      - Crawford, J. W.; Asheville (Box 121, Folder 1365)
    - Ohio
      - Bakers; Columbus (Box 122, Folder 1366)
      - Ball and Thomas; Cincinnati (Box 122, Folder 1367)
      - Beach, T. A.; Delaware (Box 122, Folder 1368)
      - Bennet, W. P.; Marietta (Box 122, Folder 1369)
      - Clark, Renzin; Bolivar (Box 122, Folder 1370)
      - Closs, John; Cincinnati (Box 122, Folder 1371)
      - Courtney, H.; Millersburgh (Box 122, Folder 1372)
      - Cridland; Dayton (Box 122, Folder 1373)
      - Doty, Prof.; Wooster (Box 122, Folder 1374)
      - Edwards, W. L.; Ashland (Box 122, Folder 1375)
      - Feiger, E. F.; Pomeroy (Box 122, Folder 1376)
      - Foreman; Lancaster (Box 122, Folder 1377)
      - Gates; Garrettsville (Box 122, Folder 1378)
      - Hall, Ross; Millersburg (Box 122, Folder 1379)
      - Hathaway; Carlisle Block and Chillicothe (Box 122, Folder 1380)
      - Hawkins, F. I.; Medina (Box 122, Folder 1381)
      - Holman; Warren (Box 122, Folder 1382)
      - Howland; Cincinnati (Box 122, Folder 1383)
      - Keney, E. H.; Dayton (Box 122, Folder 1384)
      - Landy; Cincinnati (Box 122, Folder 1385)
      - Lawson; London (Box 122, Folder 1386)
      - Lewis, Will T.; Zanesville (Box 122, Folder 1387)
      - Miller, J. C.; Felicity (Box 122, Folder 1388)
      - Miller, Lorin E.; Alliance (Box 122, Folder 1389)
      - Nichols; St. Clairsville (Box 122, Folder 1390)
      - North, W. C.; Cleveland (Box 122, Folder 1391)
      - Nugent, J. H.; Chillicothe (Box 122, Folder 1392)
      - Oakley, J. H.; Ravenna (Box 122, Folder 1393)
      - Pfeifer, J. A.; Columbus (Box 122, Folder 1394)
      - Pifer & Becker; Cleveland (Box 122, Folder 1395)
      - Platt, E. W.; Sandusky (Box 122, Folder 1396)
      - Reichard; Alliance (Box 122, Folder 1397)
      - Richardson; Chillicothe (Box 122, Folder 1398)
      - Sackett, L. N.; Medina (Box 122, Folder 1399)
      - Seibert; Lake Fork (Box 122, Folder 1400)
      - Smith; Garrettsville (Box 122, Folder 1401)
      - Smith; Marysville (Box 122, Folder 1402)
      - Stanton Photo; Springfield (Box 122, Folder 1403)
      - Star Novelty Co.; Andover (Box 122, Folder 1404)
      - Steffey; Mt. Union (Box 122, Folder 1405)
      - Stein; Ravenna (Box 122, Folder 1406)
      - Strickmaker, John; Canal Dover (Box 122, Folder 1407)
      - Strickmaker, P.; New Philadelphia (Box 122, Folder 1408)
      - Weckman, J. P.; Cincinnati (Box 122, Folder 1409)
      - Welser, G. W.; Steubenville (Box 122, Folder 1410)
      - White; Chillicothe (Box 122, Folder 1411)
      - Williams; New Athens (Box 122, Folder 1412)
      - Windisch, Charles F.; Cincinnati (Box 122, Folder 1413)
      - Wolbach, T. D.; Wadsworth (Box 122, Folder 1414)
    - Pennsylvania
      - Barbour, J. Will; Chambersburg (Box 123, Folder 1415)
      - Bonine, R. A.; Altoona (Box 123, Folder 1416)
      - Brownell, D. K.; Scranton (Box 123, Folder 1417)
      - Buttorf; York (Box 123, Folder 1418)
      - Chillman, P. Edward and Company; Philadelphia (Box 123, Folder 1419)
      - Dabbs, B. L. H.; Alleghany City and Pittsburgh (Box 123, Folder 1420)
      - Daily; Lebanon (Box 123, Folder 1421)
      - Ferguson, B. F.; Philadelphia (Box 123, Folder 1422)
      - Frampton and Work; Punxsutawney (Box 123, Folder 1423)
      - Ginter & Cook; Lewisburg (Box 123, Folder 1424)
      - Goodhart, C. Anson; Shippensburg (Box 123, Folder 1425)
      - Gutekunst, F.; Philadelphia (Box 123, Folder 1426)
      - Henning, J. H.; Johnstown (Box 123, Folder 1427)
      - Kleckner, M. A.; Bethlehem (Box 123, Folder 1428)
      - Knecht, Josiah; Orefield and Stetlersville (Box 123, Folder 1429)
      - Laughlin, J. R.; West Philadelphia (Box 123, Folder 1430)
      - Lease; Lancaster (Box 123, Folder 1431)
      - Lemer, John D.; Harrisburg (Box 123, Folder 1432)
      - Matthews, George; Allegheny City (Box 123, Folder 1433)
      - McMahon, T.; Danville (Box 123, Folder 1434)
      - Newell, R.; Philadelphia (Box 123, Folder 1435)
      - Purviance; Pittsburgh (Box 123, Folder 1436)
      - Reimer; Philadelphia (Box 123, Folder 1437)
      - Reynolds, J. M.; Allegheny (Box 123, Folder 1438)
      - Saylor; Reading (Box 123, Folder 1439)
      - Shadle and Bussor; York (Box 123, Folder 1440)
      - Singley, B. L.; Meadville (Box 123, Folder 1441)
      - Smith and Seilers; Philadelphia (Box 123, Folder 1442)
      - Sperber; Allegheny (Box 123, Folder 1443)
      - Stearns, J. E.; Honesdale (Box 123, Folder 1444)
      - Tipton; Gettysburg (Box 123, Folder 1445)
      - Vansyckel, H. C.; Philadelphia (Box 123, Folder 1446)
      - Weaver, P. S.; Hanover (Box 123, Folder 1447)
      - Webb, Harry A.; Philadelphia (Box 123, Folder 1448)
      - Wenderoth and Taylor; Philadelphia (Box 123, Folder 1449)
      - Wheeland and McMahon; Milton (Box 123, Folder 1450)
      - Unidentified photographer; Womelsdorf (Box 123, Folder 1451)
      - Unidentified photographer, Cyanotype photographs of railway bridges and construction projects near Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania, circa 1897-1898, 1910 (Box 124, Folder 1452-1458)
        Cyanotypes are photographic prints made by a photographic process using iron salts and producing an image in Prussian blue.
    - Rhode Island
      - Goodwin, D. W.; Providence (Box 125, Folder 1459)
      - Mills, William and Son; Olneyville (Box 125, Folder 1460)
      - Rose, P. H.; Providence (Box 125, Folder 1461)
    - South Carolina
      - Miller; Charlestown (Box 125, Folder 1462)
    - Tennessee
      - Lindsey & Hodges; Knoxville (Box 125, Folder 1463)
    - Wisconsin
      - Bates and Cotterell; Waukesha (Box 125, Folder 1464)
      - Bogrand, P.; Eagle River (Box 125, Folder 1465)
      - Broich, Hugo; Milwaukee (Box 125, Folder 1466)
      - Burpee; Beloit (Box 125, Folder 1467)
      - Byam, J. W.; Fond du Lac (Box 125, Folder 1468)
      - Ennor; Stevens Point (Box 125, Folder 1469)
      - Everett, J. C.; Beloit (Box 125, Folder 1470)
      - Fenner; Westfield (Box 125, Folder 1471)
      - Geist; Beloit (Box 125, Folder 1472)
      - Helsom, R. O.; Menomonie (Box 125, Folder 1473)
      - Horton; Beaver Dam (Box 125, Folder 1474)
      - Johnson; Cumberland (Box 125, Folder 1475)
      - Kruse; Milwaukee (Box 125, Folder 1476)
      - Kundler, G.; Milwaukee (Box 125, Folder 1477)
      - La Marsh, B.; Kenosha (Box 125, Folder 1478)
      - Mould, M. and Son; Baraboo (Box 125, Folder 1479)
      - Myres, H. G.; Richland Center (Box 125, Folder 1480)
      - Radbruch, H. I.; Milwaukee (Box 125, Folder 1481)
      - Reudy, F.; Cochran (Box 125, Folder 1482)
      - Schadde, P. J.; Sauk City (Box 125, Folder 1483)
      - Schneider, F. W.; Green Bay (Box 125, Folder 1484)
      - Stein; Milwaukee (Box 125, Folder 1485)
      - Sutter; Milwaukee (Box 125, Folder 1486)
      - Truesdell; Kenosha (Box 125, Folder 1487)
      - Vanderbie, L.; Platteville (Box 125, Folder 1488)
      - Webster and Walker; Oshkosh (Box 125, Folder 1489)
      - Unidentified photographer; Racine (Box 125, Folder 1490)
      - Unidentified photographer; Rochester (Box 125, Folder 1491)
    - Vermont
      - Gage, F. B.; St. Johnsbury (Box 126, Folder 1492)
      - Kane; Brattleboro (Box 126, Folder 1493)
      - Prouty; Brattleboro (Box 126, Folder 1494)
      - Watson; Bennington (Box 126, Folder 1495)
      - White, H. C.; North Bennington (Box 126, Folder 1496)
    - Virginia
      - Clinedinst; Staunton (Box 126, Folder 1497)
      - Davis, G. W.; Richmond (Box 126, Folder 1498)
      - Medernach; Danville (Box 126, Folder 1499)
      - Richmond Photography Company; Richmond (Box 126, Folder 1500)
    - Washington, D.C.
      - Merritt, J. D. (Box 126, Folder 1501)
      - Ulke, Henry (Box 126, Folder 1502)
    - West Virginia
      - Higgins; Wheeling (Box 126, Folder 1503)
      - Portable Studio; Shepherdstown (Box 126, Folder 1504)
  - Photographic Prints by Itinerant Photographers
    This subseries includes examples of photographs by itinerant photographers, who traveled throughout the United States creating portraits and view during the late nineteenth and early twentieth centuries.
    - Alexander, F. E. (Box 127, Folder 1505)
    - Blatt, C. G. (Box 127, Folder 1506)
    - Boston Railroad Photo Car (Box 127, Folder 1507)
    - Bradley, W. A. (Box 127, Folder 1508)
    - Cooper, H. D. (Box 127, Folder 1509)
    - Dougherty, William (Box 127, Folder 1510)
    - Estey, William J. (Box 127, Folder 1511)
    - Hockenbery Bros. (Box 127, Folder 1512)
    - Hoffman and Shriver (Box 127, Folder 1513)
    - Hutchings, G. W. (Box 127, Folder 1514)
    - Lees (Box 127, Folder 1515)
    - Lloyd, J. A. (Box 127, Folder 1516)
    - Maynard (Box 127, Folder 1517)
    - McMullen and Schall (Box 127, Folder 1518)
    - Mode, F. (Box 127, Folder 1519)
    - Morgan, D. P. (Box 127, Folder 1520)
    - Nick, William (Box 127, Folder 1521)
    - Old Nick (Box 127, Folder 1522)
    - Palace Railroad Photograph Car (Box 127, Folder 1523)
    - Pollock (Box 127, Folder 1524)
    - Shane, J. B. (Box 127, Folder 1525)
    - Sharp (Box 127, Folder 1526)
    - Silvis, John B. (Box 127, Folder 1527)
    - Tooley and Sauvain (Box 127, Folder 1528)
    - Vreeland (Box 127, Folder 1529)
    - Webb, W. T. (Box 127, Folder 1530)
    - Welsh and Harlow (Box 127, Folder 1531)
    - Wertz, G. N. (Box 127, Folder 1532)
    - Wilcox, George W. (Box 127, Folder 1533)
    - Williams, N. A. and Sons (Box 127, Folder 1534)
    - Unidentified traveling photographers (Box 127, Folder 1535)
  - Photographs by Photographers Outside the United States
    This subseries consists of photograph albums and photographic prints created by photographers outside of the United States, chiefly in Europe, but also examples by photographers in Argentina, Australia, Canada, Hong King, Japan, Lebanon, Mexico, and New Zealand.
    Organized under three headings: Photograph Albums, Photographic Prints, and Oversize Photographic Prints
    - Photograph Albums
      - Unidentified Creators
        - Photographs album of Palermo, Italy, circa 1900 (Box 128)
        - Album of a trip to Gibraltar, Italy, and Monaco, circa 1900 (Box 129)
        - Album of a trip to Italy, Great Britain, Belgium, Netherlands, and Switzerland, circa 1900 (Box 130)
        - Disbound album of sites in Paris, France, and London, England
          - Paris, France, circa 1900 (Box 131, Folder 1536-1556)
          - London, England, circa 1900 (Box 132, Folder 1557-1563)
    - Photographic Prints
      - Australia
        - Bradley, William (Box 133, Folder 1564)
        - Stewart & Co. (Box 133, Folder 1565)
      - Austria
        - Angerer, Victor (Box 133, Folder 1566)
      - Azores
        - Rapozo (Box 133, Folder 1567)
      - Belgium
        - Unidentified photographer (Box 133, Folder 1568)
      - Brazil
        - Carneiro, Silva & Tavares (Box 133, Folder 1569)
      - Canada
        - Barrett, A. (Box 133, Folder 1570)
        - Braithwaite, S. (Box 133, Folder 1571)
        - Brock & Co. (Box 133, Folder 1572)
        - Connolly, J. H. (Box 133, Folder 1573)
        - Dixon, S.L. (Box 133, Folder 1574)
        - Edwards, W. H. (Box 133, Folder 1575)
        - Farmer, W. (Box 133, Folder 1576)
        - Flood, C. (Box 133, Folder 1577)
        - Gauvin & Gentzel (Box 133, Folder 1578)
        - Henry, Ebenezer Elijah (Box 133, Folder 1579)
        - Hunter, T. (Box 133, Folder 1580)
        - Martin, G. (Box 133, Folder 1581)
        - McKenney & Dicks (Box 133, Folder 1582)
        - Moles, R. G. (Box 133, Folder 1583)
        - Notman & Fraser (Box 133, Folder 1584)
        - Notman, W. (Box 133, Folder 1585)
        - O'Donnell, W. D. (Box 133, Folder 1586)
        - Parsons, S. H. (Box 133, Folder 1587)
        - People's Photo Studio (Box 133, Folder 1588)
        - Redden (Box 133, Folder 1589)
        - Segee, W. V. (Box 133, Folder 1590)
        - Simpson, Herbert F. (Box 133, Folder 1591)
        - Stiff Bros. (Box 133, Folder 1592)
        - Stoerger, A. (Box 133, Folder 1593)
        - Tuck, J. P. (Box 133, Folder 1594)
        - Weiss, E. L. (Box 133, Folder 1595)
      - Czechoslovakia
        - Dobra Galerie (Box 134, Folder 1596)
      - Denmark
        - Christensen, L.N. (Box 134, Folder 1597)
        - Crone, Hilmar (Box 134, Folder 1598)
        - Jenson, Sophus (Box 134, Folder 1599)
        - Steen-Mollers (Box 134, Folder 1600)
      - England
        - Adams, E. P. (Box 134, Folder 1601)
        - Ashford Brothers & Co. (Box 134, Folder 1602)
        - Bark, C. Voss (Box 134, Folder 1603)
        - Barnes & Son (Box 134, Folder 1604)
        - Barraud (Box 134, Folder 1605)
        - Barton, W. H. (Box 134, Folder 1606)
        - Beattie, John (Box 134, Folder 1607)
        - Bedford, F. (Box 134, Folder 1608)
        - Bennett, T. (Box 134, Folder 1609)
        - Benson, J. F. (Box 134, Folder 1610)
        - Birch, Newby (Box 134, Folder 1611)
        - Boucher, A. (Box 134, Folder 1612)
        - Bowers, H. T. (Box 134, Folder 1613)
        - Brown, Arthur (Box 134, Folder 1614)
        - Brown, Barnes, & Bell (Box 134, Folder 1615)
        - Butler (Box 134, Folder 1616)
        - Byrne, J. (Box 134, Folder 1617)
        - C. N. & Co. (Box 134, Folder 1618)
        - Chappuis, P. E. (Box 134, Folder 1619)
        - Clark, William (Box 134, Folder 1620)
        - Claudet, A. (Box 134, Folder 1621)
        - Cocking, Edwin (Box 134, Folder 1622)
        - Cooper (Box 134, Folder 1623)
        - Davies, F. (Box 134, Folder 1624)
        - Dean, George A. (Box 134, Folder 1625)
        - Desa (Box 134, Folder 1626)
        - Dodson, J. (Box 134, Folder 1627)
        - Downey, W. & D. (Box 134, Folder 1628)
        - Duncan, J. (Box 134, Folder 1629)
        - Edge, T. (Box 134, Folder 1630)
        - Elliott & Fry (Box 134, Folder 1631)
        - Emberson & Sons (Box 134, Folder 1632)
        - Evans, E. J. (Box 134, Folder 1633)
        - Ferguson (Box 134, Folder 1634)
        - Ford, J. Pearce (Box 134, Folder 1635)
        - Fry, W. & A. H. (Box 134, Folder 1636)
        - Fullaway, J. (Box 134, Folder 1637)
        - Gandy, Charles A. (Box 134, Folder 1638)
        - Gibbs, E. T. (Box 134, Folder 1639)
        - Godfray (Box 134, Folder 1640)
        - Goodfellow, E. (Box 134, Folder 1641)
        - Goodfellow, Henry (Box 134, Folder 1642)
        - Grant, Edwin (Box 134, Folder 1643)
        - Guttenberg, M. (Box 134, Folder 1644)
        - Hall, W. (Box 134, Folder 1645)
        - Harman, R. (Box 134, Folder 1646)
        - Harrison, E. (Box 134, Folder 1647)
        - Helsby & Co. (Box 134, Folder 1648)
        - Henderson, A. L. (Box 134, Folder 1649)
        - Hennah & Kent (Box 134, Folder 1650)
        - Heritage, Thomas (Box 134, Folder 1651)
        - Hirst, William (Box 134, Folder 1652)
        - Holroyd, J. (Box 134, Folder 1653)
        - Houlson, R. (Box 134, Folder 1654)
        - Hughes, H. (Box 134, Folder 1655)
        - Johnson, Fred (Box 134, Folder 1656)
        - Jolliffe & Co. (Box 134, Folder 1657)
        - Lafosse (Box 134, Folder 1658)
        - Lock & Whitfield (Box 134, Folder 1659)
        - The London School of Photography (Box 134, Folder 1660)
        - London Stereoscopic Co. (Box 134, Folder 1661)
        - Long & Faulkner (Box 134, Folder 1662)
        - Macy (Box 135, Folder 1663)
        - Mayall (Box 135, Folder 1664)
        - Moody, J. (Box 135, Folder 1665)
        - Newcombe, C. T. (Box 135, Folder 1666)
        - Newell & Son (Box 135, Folder 1667)
        - Pope & Co. (Box 135, Folder 1668)
        - Robinson, H. P. (Box 135, Folder 1669)
        - Scott, Benjamin (Box 135, Folder 1670)
        - Skeolan, P. (Box 135, Folder 1671)
        - Smith, O. C. (Box 135, Folder 1672)
        - Suter, W. J. (Box 135, Folder 1673)
        - Symonds (Box 135, Folder 1674)
        - Syrus, Napoleon (Box 135, Folder 1675)
        - Taylor, A. & G. (Box 135, Folder 1676)
        - Thomas, Abraham (Box 135, Folder 1677)
        - Thomas, John (Box 135, Folder 1678)
        - Tod, Alexander George (Box 135, Folder 1679)
        - Vandyke (Box 135, Folder 1680)
        - Vandyke & Brown (Box 135, Folder 1681)
        - Viner, Frederick (Box 136, Folder 1682-1688)
        - Walker, C. B. (Box 135, Folder 1689)
        - Ward, R. (Box 135, Folder 1690)
        - Watkins, John (Box 135, Folder 1691)
        - Watson, W. T. (Box 135, Folder 1692)
        - West, G. (Box 135, Folder 1693)
        - Whitlock, H. J. (Box 135, Folder 1694)
        - Wiggins, C. F. (Box 135, Folder 1695)
        - Wilkinson (Box 135, Folder 1696)
        - Willis, G. (Box 135, Folder 1697)
        - Wilson, George Washington (Box 135, Folder 1698)
        - Witcomb, C. J. (Box 135, Folder 1699)
        - Wood, J. (Box 135, Folder 1700)
        - Wright, Jasper J. (Box 135, Folder 1701)
        - Unidentified photographer, Barnstaple (Box 135, Folder 1702)
        - Unidentified photographer (Box 135, Folder 1703)
      - France
        - Chesnay, E. (Box 135, Folder 1704)
        - Cognacq, T. (Box 135, Folder 1705)
        - Disderi (Box 135, Folder 1706)
        - Erwin Freres (Box 135, Folder 1707)
        - Hautecoeur, Jules (Box 135, Folder 1708)
        - Le Gray, G. & Cie. (Box 135, Folder 1709)
        - Marya (Box 135, Folder 1710)
        - Navar (Box 135, Folder 1711)
        - Otto & Fiere (Box 135, Folder 1712)
        - Pesme (Box 135, Folder 1713)
        - Rensch, Camille (Box 135, Folder 1714)
        - Reutlinger (Box 135, Folder 1715)
        - Rousseau, Cheri (Box 135, Folder 1716)
      - Germany
        - Brandseph, F. (Box 135, Folder 1717)
        - Brasch, August (Box 135, Folder 1718)
        - Buchner, Maler (Box 135, Folder 1719)
        - Bucker, Heinrich (Box 135, Folder 1720)
        - Damm, Otto (Box 135, Folder 1721)
        - Eberlain, Adelbert (Box 135, Folder 1722)
        - Gattineau, J. G., & Sohn (Box 135, Folder 1723)
        - Haase, L. (Box 135, Folder 1724)
        - Hoffert, W. (Box 135, Folder 1725)
        - Hruschka, Antoine (Box 135, Folder 1726)
        - Julius, Jgnatz (Box 135, Folder 1727)
        - Mondel & Jacob (Box 135, Folder 1728)
        - Photographischen Gesellschaft (Box 135, Folder 1729)
        - Schroder, H. (Box 135, Folder 1730)
        - Schwerdfeger, E. A. (Box 135, Folder 1731)
        - Wolfram, F. (Box 135, Folder 1732)
        - Unidentified photographer (Box 135, Folder 1733)
      - Hong Kong
        - Floyd, W. P. (Box 137, Folder 1734)
        - Hing-Qua, John (Box 137, Folder 1735)
      - Ireland
        - Allen, M. (Box 137, Folder 1736)
      - Italy
        - Canobi, Emilio (Box 137, Folder 1737)
        - Chauffourier, P. E. (Box 137, Folder 1738)
        - Edzione Esposito (Box 137, Folder 1739)
        - Fratelli Alinari (Box 137, Folder 1740)
        - Guggenheim, M. (Box 137, Folder 1741)
        - Unidentified photographer (Box 137, Folder 1742-1744)
      - Japan
        - Suzuki, S. (Box 137, Folder 1745)
      - Mexico
        - Chavez, Jose Perez (Box 137, Folder 1746)
        - Martinez, Andres (Box 137, Folder 1747)
        - Michaud, Julio (Box 137, Folder 1748)
      - Netherlands
        - Vetter, Jac. (Box 137, Folder 1749)
      - New Zealand
        - Ferrier, W. (Box 137, Folder 1750)
        - Snow White Studios (Box 137, Folder 1751)
      - Norway
        - Bjornsta, J. H. (Box 137, Folder 1752)
        - Dahl, J. (Box 137, Folder 1753)
        - Fehr, Joh. v. d. (Box 137, Folder 1754)
        - Larsen, Theodor (Box 137, Folder 1755)
        - Rode, J. A. (Box 137, Folder 1756)
      - Northern Ireland
        - Ayton, Alex. R. (Box 137, Folder 1757)
        - Church, E. T. (Box 137, Folder 1758)
      - Peru
        - Courret, E. (Box 137, Folder 1759)
        - Garreaud, E. (Box 137, Folder 1760)
      - Portugal
        - Sousa, A. S. (Box 137, Folder 1761)
      - Russia
        - Borkobr, M. (Box 137, Folder 1762)
        - Brodowsky, R. (Box 137, Folder 1763)
        - Burkina, I. G. (Box 137, Folder 1764)
        - Kadisson, M. (Box 137, Folder 1765)
        - Unidentified photographer (Box 137, Folder 1766)
      - Scotland
        - Dunn, W. L. (Box 137, Folder 1767)
        - Gemmell (Box 137, Folder 1768)
        - Graham, G. (Box 137, Folder 1769)
        - Roger, A. (Box 137, Folder 1770)
        - Ross & Thomson (Box 137, Folder 1771)
        - Stuart (Box 137, Folder 1772)
        - Wall, Alfred H (Box 137, Folder 1773)
        - Wilson, George Washington (Box 137, Folder 1774)
        - Unidentified photographer (Box 137, Folder 1775)
      - Sweden
        - Appelblad, Thure (Box 137, Folder 1776)
        - Hansen, Fr. (Box 137, Folder 1777)
        - Hesse, Hjalmar Jn. (Box 137, Folder 1778)
        - Sandberg, Herm. (Box 137, Folder 1779)
      - Wales
        - Aiken, H. (Box 137, Folder 1780)
        - Bell, C.P. (Box 137, Folder 1781)
        - Kennerly, H. (Box 137, Folder 1782)
        - Oglesby, S. (Box 137, Folder 1783)
        - Smith, Alfred Ford (Box 137, Folder 1784)
        - Unidentified photographer (Box 137, Folder 1785)
    - Oversize Photographic Prints
      - Argentina
        - Weber, Walter (Box 138 (Oversize), Folder 1786)
      - Austria
        - Unidentified photographers, Vienna (Box 138 (Oversize), Folder 1787-1789)
      - France
        - Hautecoeur, Jules (Box 138 (Oversize), Folder 1790)
          Oversize envelope advertising photographs by Hautecoeur
        - Unidentified photographers, Paris (Box 138 (Oversize), Folder 1791-1792)
      - Great Britain
        - Wilson, George Washington (Box 138 (Oversize), Folder 1793-1795)
      - Italy
        - Naya, Carlo (Box 138 (Oversize), Folder 1796-1797)
        - Poppi, Pietro (Box 138 (Oversize), Folder 1798-1799)
          Also operated as Fotografia dell'Emilia
        - Unidentified photographer, Florence (Box 138 (Oversize), Folder 1800)
        - Unidentified photographer, Pisa (Box 138 (Oversize), Folder 1801)
        - Unidentified photographers, Rome (Box 138 (Oversize), Folder 1802-1804)
        - Unidentified photographer, Venice (Box 138 (Oversize), Folder 1805)
      - Lebanon